A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Middle East and Africa, Tunis, Tunisia Field Office Files FA645
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Population, 1962-1976; VII
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Reports III, 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Reports IV (1/2), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Reports IV (2/2), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Reports V, 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Correspondence, 1971 June-1973 December (Box 16)
  - "Family Planning in Morocco, 1965-1972: The Role of Ford Foundation and Population Council Assistance" by Richard S. Roberts, Jr. (1/2), 1972 December (Box 16)
  - "Family Planning in Morocco, 1965-1972: The Role of Ford Foundation and Population Council Assistance" by Richard S. Roberts, Jr. (2/2, second copy), 1972 December (Box 16)
  - Family Planning in Tunisia, 1963 (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. I (63-270A), 1962 March-1964 December (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. II (63-270A), 1965 January-1968 June (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. III (63-270A) (1/2), 1969 June-1970 April (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. III (63-270A) (2/2), 1969 June-1970 April (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. IV (63-270A), 1970 May-1971 May (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. V (63-270A), 1971 June-1973 April (Box 17)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports I, 1962-1966 (Box 17)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports II, 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports III, 1969-1970 (Box 17)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports IV, 1970 April-1971 April (Box 17)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports V, 1971 May-1972 January (Box 18)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports VI, 1972 February-July (Box 18)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports VII, 1972 August-1973 December (Box 18)
  - Population -- Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning, 1967-1969 (Box 18)
  - Population -- Republic of Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning, 1970-1975 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning, 1973-1976 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning (690-0657), 1969-1973 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning (690-0657) -- Correspondence (1/2), 1973-1976 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning (690-0657) -- Correspondence (2/2), 1973-1976 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning (690-0657) -- Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning (690-0657) -- General, Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 18)
  - Family Planning and Demography -- Tunisia, Morocco, Algeria -- General Reports (1/3), 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Family Planning and Demography -- Tunisia, Morocco, Algeria -- General Reports (2/3), 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Family Planning and Demography -- Tunisia, Morocco, Algeria -- General Reports (3/3), 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Family Planning and Demography -- Tunisia, Morocco, Algeria -- General Reports, 1974 (Box 19)
  - "The Ford Foundation/Population Council North African Population Program in Retrospect: 1963-1975" by Alain Marcoux, 1975 December (Box 19)
  - Population Evaluation of North Africa Programs and Marcoux Report, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - "Report on the North African Regional Program, 1970-1971" by the Population Council Re: Ford Foundation Grant, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Alumni Association, ENAP, Morrocco, 1973 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Other Agencies, 1974 June-1976 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Other Agencies -- Women's International Forum on Population and Development and Ford Foundation International Division Women's Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Other Agencies -- Resource Institutions (Harvard Center for Population Studies), 1973 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Other Agencies -- Rennes, School of Health, 1973-1974 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Evaluation Mission Review 1972 for North Africa, Part I, 1971 September-1972 April (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Evaluation Mission Review 1972 for North Africa, Part II (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- French Family Planning, Part I, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- French Family Planning, Part II, Dec 1972-1974 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General Information, 1972-1974 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General Information IV, Jun 1974-1976 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- ICOMP -- Wickham, R.S., 1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- General -- Dr. Jongmans Report and Correspondence, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- General -- Population Office Mailings, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- General -- Population Office Questionnaire on Management of Family Programs, 1972 (Box 20)
  - Population -- General, Special Topics -- Population Strategy Review, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Beyond Family Planning -- Reports, 1969-1975 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Beyond Family Planning, 1972 October (Box 20)
  - Population -- Reports Re: Ford Foundation Supported Population Studies Centers, Bellagio Conference, Women's Roles, etc., 1973 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Bellagio Population Group -- Project Proposals, International Division Conference Memo, Reports, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Elisabeth Mueller (Population Council) -- Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Ford and Rockefeller Foundations -- Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, Part I, 1970-1971 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Ford and Rockefeller Foundations Program in Support of Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, Part II, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Project Proposal -- Taylor/Berelson Scheme Re: Family Planning, 1972 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Program Proposal -- Population Association of Africa, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Proposal for a Ford Foundation Mission to Survey Project Possibilities in Demographic and Social Science Research in Population in West Africa, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Population -- "Rolling Mission" (Family Planning Review Mission, January 22-26, 1973) -- Maghreb, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - "Health and Nutrition in India: Recommendations for Ford Foundation Support" by Davidson R. Gwatkin, 1974 January (Box 20)
  - Family Planning, Fertility, and Abortion in Africa and Developing Countries -- Reports, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Family Planning, Population -- Africa (and elsewhere) -- Reports, Travel Logs, Ford Foundation Reprint, Conference Memoranda and Agenda, 1964-1970 (Box 20)
  - Family Planning, Population -- Reports, 1965-1974 (Box 20)
  - Family Planning, Population, Social Science Research on Population and Development -- Memoranda and Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (1/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (2/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (3/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (4/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (5/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (6/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conference -- Third Annual Wheat Workshop (7/7), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences, Seminars and Workshops -- General, 1971-1974 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences, Seminars and Workshops -- General, 1974 June-1975 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- African Population Conferences, 1971-1974 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- Micro-Economics Seminar Re: Fertility (Tunis, February 1972), 1972 February (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- Population Meeting (Elsinore, Denmark, June 1972), 1972 June (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- Third Population Conference (Bellagio, Italy) -- Summary and Projections -- Moderator, David Bell, 1973 May 12 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- Tentative Plans for Workshop jointly Sponsored by Inst. Nat. du P.F. et de la P.M.I. Ministry of Health, Tunisia, and Community and Family Study Center, University of Chicago (Tunis, July/Aug 1973), 1972 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- International Union for the Scientific Study of Population -- Liege Conference, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Population -- Conferences and Seminars -- International Conference on the Physician and Population Change (Stockholm, September 4-6, 1974), 1974 September 4-6 (Box 21)
- Public Administration, 1964-1968; VIII
  - "Etude Preliminaire sur la Reform Administrative en Algerie", 1966 January (Box 21)
  - "Ford Foundation Public Administration Program in Tunisia" -- A Report to David Heaps from Maxwell Lehman, 1968 October (Box 21)
  - Public Administration -- Algeria -- Administrative Reform, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
  - Public Administration -- Algeria -- Civil Service, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Public Administration -- Pan-Maghrebian Meetings, 1964-1967 (Box 21)
  - Public Administration -- Tunisia -- National School of Administration -- Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 21)